<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="need_help">Need help?\nClick here to view the tutorial.</string>
    <string name="start_tutorial">Start tutorial</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_start_the_tutorial">Do you want to start the tutorial?</string>
    <string name="tutorial_intro">Hey!
        \nThis is a short tutorial on how to get started with NextTask.
        \nPress the \">\" in the bottom right corner to continue or press the 
        \"X\" in the bottom left corner to quit. If you want to see the 
        tutorial again, just shake your device!	</string>
    <string name="tutorial_add_task">Nice, let\'s get started! Press the \"+\" in the upper 
        right corner and add your first task.\n\n	</string>
    <string name="tutorial_enter_task">Good job!
        \nNow, what can you do with tasks? Try pressing it to find out.	</string>
    <string name="tutorial_introduce_task">Tasks are things you have to do. 
        This is the detailed overview of a tasks. You can write descriptions, 
        set a due date and add reminders. When a task is overdue, it will appear 
        red in the list of tasks. Also, all its parent folders will have a small \"!\" 
        on them, so that you easily can find overdue tasks.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_set_due_date">Now try setting a due date. Press the marked element and select a date.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_set_reminder">Great! Next, try adding a reminder. There are custom reminders 
        and reminders relative to the due date. You can set as many reminders as you wish.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_change_name">Nice, you are starting to get a hang of this.
        See the title at the top of the screen? Try tapping it to change the name of this task. 
        Then, press the check mark to save the new name.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_go_back">Well, now you know how tasks work. Go back to learn about 
        more of NextTask\'s awesome features. You can either swipe right or press the back button 
        in the upper left corner.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_check_task">Okay, now we\'re back at the overview. Tap the circle to the left of a task. </string>
    <string name="tutorial_prioritize_task">Nice, that\'s how you check a task. It means that you have completed it. 
        If you press it again, it gets unchecked. Tap the star to the right of a task. The star symbolizes that the 
        item is prioritized.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_add_folder">Awesome, you have now mastered tasks. But just listing tasks will get messy 
        pretty fast. We need something to group them in. What about folders? Yeah, they seem like a good idea. 
        Instead of pressing the \"+\", hold your finger on it, and drag it down. That\'s a faster way to add folders.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_enter_folder">Cool, adding items that way was much faster. Now, press on the folder to see its content.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_introduce_folder">Okay, this is an empty folder. In folders, you group items. You can have as many nested folders as you like.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_add_note">Well, an empty folder is kinda boring, don\'t you think? 
        Try adding a note to it. Hold your finger over the \"+\" again, but this time, drag to the middle, over the pen icon.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_enter_note">Good job! That\'s how a note is added. If you want, you can of course add all
        the items by tapping the \"+\" and selecting what type you want to add. Now press the note you just created!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_introduce_note">Alright, so this is a note. A note is basically just an empty writing space. 
        You can write down anything you\'d like; ideas, cool quotes you\'ve heard or whatever you want.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_change_description">Speaking of writing down stuff, try it for yourself! Just tap the gray
        area and write something. When you are done, press the checkmark in the upper right corner to save your changes.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_go_back2">Amazing! Now you also know how notes and folders work. Go back to the folder where 
        the task was and I\'ll show you some more features.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_enable_options">To remove, move and group items, there is a set of powerful tools. 
        To be able to use them, hold a finger down on any item in the list.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_change_order">That wasn\'t hard, was it? Now you are in the options mode. By tapping items, 
        you can toggle and untoggle them. If you perform a bulk action, all the selected items will be affected. 
        You can also reorder individual items by dragging them around. Just grab them in those three 
        lines on their right side. Try it out!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_remove_items">Cool, that went great! Now, to remove an item, you select it and press the trash can.
        Press the \">\" to learn about the next action.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_group_items">Okay, the next action is a bit more complicated. If you press it, you group the 
        selected items in a new folder. All you have to do is naming the new folder. This comes in handy when you 
        have to organize lots of tasks.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_select_all">Alright, the next button selects and unselects all the items in the list.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_move_items">What if you want to move something? Well, that\'s what the next action is for. 
        You simply choose what folder you want to move your items to. You can also move folders to the menu, which
        we\'ll get to in a minute.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_disable_options">Alright, you should know everything about the actions in the option mode now. 
        Hold your finger over an item again to disable return to the normal view. You can also use the back button on 
        your device to do this.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_show_menu">We\'re almost done. Do you remember the menu i mentioned 
        earlier? Well, that\'s what you will learn to use now. Simply swipe right or press the menu button in the upper left 
        corner to see it!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_enable_menu_options">Ohh, it\'s so beautiful, isn\'t it? This is the menu, the top of the hierarchy. 
        At the bottom there are two buttons, one for adding folders in the menu, and the other one for viewing the settings. 
        In the folder list, you can also enable options, just as you did with the other ones. Remember? Just hold your finger 
        over an item.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_open_settings">Good job! Now to the final part of this tutorial, the settings! Press the settings 
        button at the bottom of the menu. It\'s the button with a gear icon.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_change_theme">In the settings you can to lots of different things; change theme, language, how to 
        sort your items and much more. Try changing the theme.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_outro">Ohh, this new theme looks so sexy. The colors match great, don\'t you think?
        \n\nWell, this was it for this tutorial. I hoped you learned alot about NextTask and will use it to organize 
        your life. If you have any questions, please contact us through the feedback form here in the settings.
        \n\nGood luck!</string>

</resources>